# Jelvin Base

http://jelv.in hi@jelv.in Manila, Philippines

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **UI/UX** Designer

Proudcloud (November 2016 - Present)

- · Create user interface designs and mockups under different projects
- · Collaborate with developers and stakeholders during design sprints
- · Convert visual designs into working prototypes and front-end code
- Design or redesign visual identities for products and services
- Create and prepare interaction design flows for user testing
- Conducted research on different approaches for better UX
- · Organize and facilitate usability testing sessions with clients
- Handled and troubleshot UI related errors and inconsistencies

### Front-end Developer, Graphic Designer

Apical Design (February 2017 - June 2017)

- Designed the initial visual identity for the brand of the company
- Created mockups of the website based on the visual identity
- · Created user interface designs and layouts for web and mobile
- Developed mobile responsive pages from mockups to code

## **Associate Software Engineer, Product Designer**

Senti Business Solutions, Inc. (November 2015 - July 2016)

- Managed and redesigned the visual identity of the company
- Designed layouts and mockups based on the new visual identity
- Created promotional materials used in marketing and events
- · Created assets and graphics for different social media platform
- Designed company assets such as business cards, shirts, and ID's
- Collaborated with developers on creating new pages and modules
- Handled front-end revisions of the company product Dashboard
- Converted the product Dashboard into mobile responsive pages
- Created dynamic visualizations for event specific internal projects
- Revised the visualizations to handle dynamic data and interactions
- Developed user interface designs for the revised Dashboard

### **EDUCATION**

# **BS Computer Science - Software Technology**

De La Salle University (June 2010 - December 2015)

- Worked as a Research Assistant for an inter-college thesis project
- Received Best Paper in Sustainability, Environment & Energy Proceedings during the DLSU Research Congress 2016
- · Created a prototype for the collaborating organization of the thesis
- Received 2<sup>nd</sup> Honor Dean's List Award for Academic year 2013 2014
- Acting Web Manager for the school publication, The LaSallian

#### **PROFILE**

I'm a designer based in Manila and I handle graphic design projects with frequent coding in between if needed.

Not only am I enthusiastic about great user experience, I'm also keen in exploring different approaches for making processes more contextual and consistent.

Whenever I have spare time off from my usual work, I also accept freelance projects that involve custom lettering and calligraphy with the hopes of mastering the field of typography.

I have recently taken an interest in business as well and found the need to slowly integrate my work flow with an entrepreneurial perspective and mindset to further empathize with the clients that I work with.

### SKILLS AND PROFICIENCY

In user interface design, I typically work on Sketch for layouts and mock-ups along with Adobe Illustrator if there's a need for vector graphics.

In coding and development, I mostly deal with Javascript and CSS for front end development work.

For visuals and graphics such as stock photography and illustration, I work on Adobe Lightroom and Adobe Photoshop respectively.

#### NOTES

Other freelance and unrelated work may be requested for reference.